<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Switzerland &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/switzerland/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 16:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2023 &#8211; On the Bernina Express, Switzerland to Colico, Italy</title>
		<link>/2023/01/04/2023-on-the-bernina-express-switzerland-to-colico-italy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Jackie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Italy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italy-switzerland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nature]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sightseeing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Switzerland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=5037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our ride on the Bernina Express took us high up into the Swiss Alps and then down to Torino, Italy.  The views from the train are exceptional and the route includes features like the 213 feet high Landwasser Viaduct and the Brusio spiral viaduct.  Gaining and losing as much altitude as the train does means [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe title="2023   On the Bernina Express, Switzerland to Colico, Italy" width="960" height="720" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JcQudG8yzds?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Our ride on the Bernina Express took us high up into the Swiss Alps and then down to Torino, Italy.  The views from the train are exceptional and the route includes features like the 213 feet high Landwasser Viaduct and the Brusio spiral viaduct.  Gaining and losing as much altitude as the train does means there are lots of switchbacks, loops, and tunnels.  I took many photos and then, once the trip was over, I tried to pick only the best to save.  Admittedly, it was a challenge.</p>
<p>The ticketing situation for both Bernina and Glacier Express is a bit confusing.  There are two separate transactions.  First, you need to reserve a seat on the train.  The price for that is about $20.  You can reserve fairly early and you really need to because the train sells out well in advance.  Then, when you get closer to your reserved time, you have to buy the actual train ticket.  You can get a point to point ticket, a &#8220;super saver&#8221; if you book early, or a Saver Day pass which is good anywhere in Switzerland on trains and buses.  There are a limited number of these, so, again, committing early saves money.</p>
<p>I used the Trainline app for most of my train tickets.  It works in most of Europe, including the UK.  However, I used the Swiss rail app, SSB to get my Saver Day passes &#8211; that is the only place to get them.  I like using the apps because they let me work in English and not have to guess the meaning of German, Italian, etc. phrases.  Also, Trainline lets you pick your currency.  By picking US dollars I have a better idea of what, exactly, I am spending.  Having said all that, let me add that train travel on this trip has been among the least of our expenditures.  I&#8217;ve been constantly surprised at how low train prices are across Europe.</p>
<p>The train crosses into Italy at Torino.  We switched to an Italian train to take us to a beautiful lakeside town, Colico.  The town is on the shore of Lake Como, a 40 mile long, very deep glacial lake which is surrounded by snowcapped mountains.  This has been a popular vacation destination for hundreds of years.  Right now, of course, is off season but there was still a lot of activity in the town.</p>
<p>Tomorrow, we will continue our train journey along the shore of Lake Como back to Milan and to the airport for our flight back to Manchester.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
