<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Michigan - Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/michigan/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 19:36:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2018 &#8211; Bear Cave Thousand Trails &#8211; Buchanan, MI</title>
		<link>/2018/06/09/2018-bear-cave-thousand-trails-buchanan-mi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 19:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michigan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=3004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bear Cave Thousand Trails is just north of South Bend, Indiana in the southwestern corner of Michigan. The campground is situated along the St. Joseph River and there are several sites along the river. Most of these sites are a bit smaller and all are 30 amp/water sites. Campers with smaller rigs will enjoy these [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/2018/06/09/2018-bear-cave-thousand-trails-buchanan-mi/">2018 – Bear Cave Thousand Trails – Buchanan, MI</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignleft " src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-VkluYtApozY/WxsLupR7laI/AAAAAAAAycs/ydm0fJg8T4APpee48s-wx7o-LWy6aISnwCKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20180605_204138.jpg" width="258" height="459" />Bear Cave Thousand Trails is just north of South Bend, Indiana in the southwestern corner of Michigan. The campground is situated along the St. Joseph River and there are several sites along the river. Most of these sites are a bit smaller and all are 30 amp/water sites. Campers with smaller rigs will enjoy these sites. There are several FHU 50 amp sites but many of these are sold to seasonal residents. Still, there were vacant FHU sites while we were at the campground. Most of the available FHU sites are large sites on or around a field rather than in the wooded areas beside the river. Not only would we have not fit in the river or playground sites, we wouldn&#8217;t have been able to get a satellite TV signal so we were satisfied with our back in site along the perimeter of the field sites.</p>
<p>The road into the campground is a bit of a concern. It is gravel and just barely wide enough for two RV&#8217;s to meet. &#8220;Just barely&#8221; may even be a bit optimistic depending on how close to the edge the drivers are willing to get. This isn&#8217;t a huge deal because the road in is fairly short, but it is something people might want to know.</p>
<p>Our Verizon signal was barely there even using a cradle booster. We had internet but it was only fair at best and sometimes unusable. Compounding the problem is the fact that there is no WiFi anywhere in the campground &#8211; not at the Activity Center and not for pay. I think Jackie and I both went through a bit of Internet withdrawal &#8211; not necessarily a bad thing.</p>
<p>The campground has a big pool (too cold for us in early June &#8211; but well-used by the kids) and a big Activity Center.  The spa was out of service. These are a ways from the FHU section of the campground.</p>
<p>During our visit the cave itself was closed due to winter flooding. Work was being done on it and on the nice river walkway that was also damaged. The nicest feature of the campground, in my opinion, was a pretty waterfall that is right at the heart of the campground. In fact, there are some campsites that overlook the waterfall. I imagine that with the sound of the water that tenting in those sites must be great for sleeping!</p>
<p>Really, I think there&#8217;s a lot to like about this campground. It is a bit tired and in need of some corporate financial TLC but really, this is a pretty good Thousand Trails.</p>
<p><iframe width="504" height="284" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sOegvYGNARQ" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><center><a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/S69XTbaJADZRrgjp7">See the individual photos with captions here.</a></center></p><p>The post <a href="/2018/06/09/2018-bear-cave-thousand-trails-buchanan-mi/">2018 – Bear Cave Thousand Trails – Buchanan, MI</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
