<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>humor &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/humor/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 23:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>West Texas Camping Tall Tale</title>
		<link>/2011/12/18/west-texas-camping-tall-tale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[humor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/west-texas-camping-tall-tale/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We were camping out in the Texas panhandle, northeast of Amarillo a ways. &#160;It started out a typical panhandle day, lots of sunshine, dry air, and a modest 40 or 50 mph steady breeze from the southeast. &#160;I told my wife to be careful with the camper door when she went in and out and, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 12px; line-height: 17px;"></span></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">We were camping out in the Texas panhandle, northeast of Amarillo a ways. &nbsp;It started out a typical panhandle day, lots of sunshine, dry air, and a modest 40 or 50 mph steady breeze from the southeast. &nbsp;I told my wife to be careful with the camper door when she went in and out and, wouldn&#8217;t you know it, it was me who stepped out without having a good tight grip of the door.</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">As luck would have it, the steady breeze gusted a bit about that time and the next thing I knew not only had the door been ripped out of my hand, but the wind blew into the camper with such force that the blew my camper wrong side out! &nbsp;It was so sad seeing all the cabinetry and fixtures there on the outside of the camper! &nbsp;</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">We collected all our personal belongings the best we were able, but some were well on their way to Guymon, OK quicker than we could grab them.</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">So there I was with a wrong side out camper and not sure what to do next. &nbsp;About that time a fellow camper who just happened to have one of those fancy medium duty trucks came over and offered to help. &nbsp;We crawled inside the wrong side out camper with a chain and hooked it to the bumper, which was now inside rather than outside. &nbsp;We secured the other end to a handy fence post. &nbsp;Then we hooked another to the kingpin which was also inside the wrong side out camper. &nbsp;We connected the other end to his big truck. &nbsp;He revved up the diesel to the point that black smoke was billowing out his exhaust. &nbsp;</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">It took some doing and some spinning of his tires, but finally that camper popped right side out again.</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">After doing some re-caulking and re-tightening of some screws the camper was a good as new.</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">Needless to say, I&#8217;ve always been more careful when opening the door on my camper on windy days.</span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><br /></span><br /><span style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">That&#8217;s my story and I&#8217;m sticking to it.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
