<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Maine &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/maine/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 19:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2018 &#8211; Moody Beach Thousand Trails &#8211; Wells, ME</title>
		<link>/2018/08/19/2018-moody-beach-thousand-trails-wells-me/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 19:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=3222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The timing of our August stay at Moody Beach Thousand Trails put us in a popular area at its most popular time. Traffic up and down Highway 1 was more often than not backed up. The campground, too, was filled to capacity nightly. This campground is tight. There are many &#8220;parallel parking&#8221; spots that were [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-ozvqpRg7T_Y/W3m_x-qsVKI/AAAAAAAA1Pw/E3BaLFhTZAcBrE9QxrpdXq6lQ-W-JrZygCKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20180813_183948.jpg" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-large" /><br />
The timing of our August stay at Moody Beach Thousand Trails put us in a popular area at its most popular time.  Traffic up and down Highway 1 was more often than not backed up.  The campground, too, was filled to capacity nightly.  This campground is tight.  There are many &#8220;parallel parking&#8221; spots that were laid out before rigs got as large as they are today.  Some would work but many would be a challenge for the average big rig.  In the &#8220;back&#8221; of the campground there are several pull-through &#8220;back to back&#8221; sites.  The camper on the driver&#8217;s side is very close.  You then share a front yard with the camper on the passenger side of the camper.</p>
<p>Depending on how people park their rigs this setup works fairly well.  One complicating factor is that many sites have been rented out to long-term campers.  Those folks tend to spread out to the very limit of their campsites.  If you happen to have permanents on both sides of you it can feel even more packed in that it is already.</p>
<p>Because of the narrow roads and placement of trees I couldn&#8217;t get into the first site we tried.  I moved to a different one and got in okay.  Getting out was a bit of a challenge because of how the permanent site next to us was set up, keeping me from making the left hand exit I should have been able to make.</p>
<p>Getting satellite TV anywhere in the campground is a challenge.  Some people manage it, but you shouldn&#8217;t arrive expecting to get satellite TV.  My Verizon signal was marginal but generally usable.  We paid for campground WiFi.  I would give it a B- grade.  Weekend evenings were pretty sluggish.  I think all the sites are FHU &#8211; many are 50 amp.</p>
<p>Aside from the above, here are a couple of things you might want to know.  First, the campground is behind a large miniature golf course and not visible from Highway 1.  Look for the big Wonder Mountain Fun Park sign.  Next to that sign is, indeed, the Moody Beach Campground sign.  You turn there, as though you are going to the miniature golf course.  Second, the campground offers shuttle van service to Footbridge Beach.  The price is nominal and parking at the beach is high and packed.  </p>
<p>Honestly, we thought our stay at Moody Beach was the least of our four campground stays in Maine on this trip.  We didn&#8217;t enjoy Wells and Kennebunkport because of the traffic congestion.  The campground continued the &#8220;congested&#8221; theme and by the end of the week we were ready to move on.</p>
<p><center><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vRMmMIruWyDJmjH0MoF5iHRYxRlZTDYq-Lf9Xkn959SU2hRQmcwok2-HA4rTEQS46D-SBEWcaVrUiCG/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" />Click this for full screen photos<br />
<a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/Yk7gfBDXYjU1TkqT7">See individual photos with captions here.</a></center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
