<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Civil War &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//tag/civil-war/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 21:13:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Lynchburg, Appomattox, and area</title>
		<link>//2013/09/08/lynchburg-appomattox-and-area/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 21:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Jackie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[museum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sightseeing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virginia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I have heard so much about Liberty University I wanted to see it for myself and of course see its library and possibly do a blog entry about it in my Great Library Ideas blog.  The young man in the Visitors center was very friendly and helpful.  We walked to the DeMoss building that houses [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I have heard so much about Liberty University I wanted to see it for myself and of course see its library and possibly do a blog entry about it in my <a href="http://pastorscott.com/library/">Great Library Ideas</a> blog.  The young man in the Visitors center was very friendly and helpful.  We walked to the DeMoss building that houses the current library in the bottom floor. The campus is beautiful and covers many acres. As we walked we noticed how clean cut the students were.  Several smiled and spoke as we passed.  The Lynchburg transit runs through campus and provides the students easy access to the various areas of the large campus.  The campus is about to get a beautiful new library so, while the old library continues to function I decided to pass on doing a blog about it. Two things that got our attention were the giant &#8220;LU&#8221; logo which takes up much of the side of the mountain above the campus and the Liberty Mountain Snowflex Center next to it.  The Snowflex is a snowless ski slope where students can go for the view, to ski, snowboard, or tube year around.  I think Liberty University is worth a visit if you happen to be in the area.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://lh3.ggpht.com/-LWS9iKJAeFc/UivUukOpK6I/AAAAAAAAW8w/owIBZx1HmCs/s144-c-o/IMG_1342.JPG"/> On Friday we decided to go to Thomas Jefferson&#8217;s Popular Forest. He started building this place in 1806 as a retreat from his very pubic life.  It was privately owned by people outside the Jefferson family from early 1800s until it was acquired by a non-profit group in the early 1980s. The grounds are quiet and restful and tour was very informative.  We gained a different perspective on Thomas Jefferson and his life.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s a lot to see in this area that we hope to visit on a future trip to this area.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQhJ1xepN2aeI7mxjTLGtFvHIsJT_b0wDbDbrPbc4E1ZTg19103W-_7jKSNbjQ32Hn3h3SqFuoYz5kV/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe><img decoding="async" src="//wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" />Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
