<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Illinois - Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/illinois/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 20:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; Bo Wood CoE &#8211; Sullivan, IL</title>
		<link>/2019/10/01/2019-bo-wood-coe-sullivan-il/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 20:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Army Corps of Engineers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illinois]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We wanted a nice campground near Decatur, IL and, even though this one was a bit farther than we wanted, we couldn&#8217;t have been much happier with a campground than we were with Bo Wood CoE Campground at Sullivan, IL. We often tell people that Corps of Engineers campgrounds are our favorites and this one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/2019/10/01/2019-bo-wood-coe-sullivan-il/">2019 – Bo Wood CoE – Sullivan, IL</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-8q0oV7VqvT0/XZOzSAinDkI/AAAAAAABBws/VZBolSmU7AM5ujDe2J6--4_PCO8puP-pgCKgBGAsYHg/s1600/IMG_20190926_153704.jpg" width="1600" height="902" class="aligncenter size-large" /><br />
We wanted a nice campground near Decatur, IL and, even though this one was a bit farther than we wanted, we couldn&#8217;t have been much happier with a campground than we were with Bo Wood CoE Campground at Sullivan, IL.  We often tell people that Corps of Engineers campgrounds are our favorites and this one is a great example of why we say that.  The sites are very large, level, and spacious.  In fact, I&#8217;d say that the theme of this Shelbyville Lake campground is &#8220;big.&#8221;  There are actually multiple campgrounds on the property that vary in amenities from electric only, to water-electric, to full hookup.  While a few sites in the &#8220;older&#8221; section offer a lake view, most are either in the woods or in open areas away from the lake.  The large &#8220;new&#8221; section has many FHU sites, including several huge pull through sites.  The property also has a boat ramp and two fenced in dog play areas.  </p>
<p>I think you could have parked four motorhomes the size of ours on our back in site.  In the mornings we had more sunshine than we wanted, but by late afternoon we were in the shade.  If we had any complaint about our campsite it was the big oak tree that dropped acorns on us from time to time.  Judging from the ground cover, we actually missed the worst of the bombardment.  </p>
<p>My Verizon signal was pretty good and I was able to get satellite TV without much trouble.  No doubt it would be nigh on to impossible in many of the more wooded areas of the campground.  </p>
<p>Bo Wood is off the beaten track far enough that it is off the radar of people just passing through the area.  It is easy to see, though, why this is a popular spot for the locals! </p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSjD1FQLOWNgFzvGjsijJN5tahN7_EyIrU32qVQnWn4EoojXEFukKtCLzNwDTfyaliafdd0g5n2xj19/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" /></p><p>The post <a href="/2019/10/01/2019-bo-wood-coe-sullivan-il/">2019 – Bo Wood CoE – Sullivan, IL</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
