<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>vehicle &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/travel/tag/vehicle/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/travel</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 15:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Campground review: Yosemite Lakes Thousand Trails, Groveland, CA</title>
		<link>/travel/2014/09/08/campground-review-yosemite-lakes-thousand-trails-groveland-ca/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 22:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[California]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Park]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vehicle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=1024</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Usually we use our 4G hotspot for the internet but that&#8217;s a complete no-go at this campground.  Using our Wilson Sleek cradle I could get 1 or 2 bars of unreliable 3G &#8211; really not enough to even have a decent phone conversation.  That left us dependent on the park&#8217;s WiFi.  By staying in the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/--Cg6NXXnAfk/X5BOvDVSpcI/AAAAAAABHCI/btG0IyJLECwR0Rsc-uQp0E6iUwbcZ1zLACPcBGAsYHg/s2048/PHOTO_20140826_103118.jpg" width="2048" height="1155" class="aligncenter size-large" /><br />
Usually we use our 4G hotspot for the internet but that&#8217;s a complete no-go at this campground.  Using our Wilson Sleek cradle I could get 1 or 2 bars of unreliable 3G &#8211; really not enough to even have a decent phone conversation.  That left us dependent on the park&#8217;s WiFi.  By staying in the section of the campground closer to the Activity Center we had slow, but somewhat useable internet.    Also, to our surprise, when I went to plug in the electric we had 50 amps &#8211; something not even listed on the campground map.</p>
<p>We were disappointed and surprised at how far it really is to Yosemite valley.  Even though a National Park entrance is only five miles from the campground it&#8217;s actually about 30 miles down to the valley &#8211; and those miles are twisting, turning, and sometimes steep miles.  Here&#8217;s a tip: the YARTS bus stops right at the campground and will take you to Yosemite valley.  The cost for the two of us was actually about what we would have spent on fuel driving in and out.  I suggest you drive in and see the more distant sites and then ride the bus for future visits to the valley.  They offer senior adult discounts and even have a three trips for the price of two special.  Also, there&#8217;s no park admission fee for those on the bus!</p>
<p>No review of Yosemite Lakes Thousand Trails is complete without mention of Highway 120&#8217;s New Priest Grade.  This 7-8 miles of road is a non-stop 5-6%, switchback filled challenge that must be faced to come to the campground.   The uphill side is also the side with the dropoffs.  It will test the vehicle&#8217;s engine and the driver&#8217;s nerves.  The downhill side hugs the side of the hill and it will test the vehicle&#8217;s transmission and brakes and the driver&#8217;s skills.  There are two other nearby roads.  One is the shorter and much steeper (15%) Old Priest &#8211; no one with a RV has any business on it and law enforcement agrees &#8211; RVs are banned from driving it.  There&#8217;s another route that includes Greely Hill road.  We checked it out and I decided it was better to just stay with New Priest.  Here&#8217;s my take on it: if you are driving a RV that you know is underpowered or overweight or especially long you should think twice before tackling this section of road.  However, most people with a properly set up RV and moderate driving experience can drive it.  Hundreds of RVs, tour buses, and logging trucks do it every week.  The YARTS bus drivers told me that their top of the hill speed target is 25 mph which they gear to hold down the grade.  They also suggested that one keep an eye on oncoming traffic, making room for bigger vehicles, especially those coming downhill.  On one had, this drive should be taken seriously.  On the other hand, a lot of people do it with no problems whatsoever.  We came up the grade about 25 mph and the engine was working hard.  Our clutch fan came on early and stayed on all the way up and a ways beyond.  We came down at 20-25 mph.  I had to tap my brakes on some of the hairpins.  Really, I thought coming down was easier than coming up.</p>
<p>The reward is a nice campground near a beautiful National Park.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTRfDXW1jDe3FHkoXpMbHHG0SuhKlOb7DARJgjzSE3y0MOM76LtJlX_ulN9CQ2CLLtAjaIfVIx8r-VU/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe><img decoding="async" src="/travel/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" />Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
