<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Canary Wharf &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/canary-wharf/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:44:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>London/Paris 2011 trip report–part 10</title>
		<link>/2011/10/04/londonparis-2011-trip-report-part-10/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canary Wharf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[London]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paris]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/londonparis-2011-trip-report-part-10/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From the beginning we&#8217;ve planned to make Tuesday a laundry-and-not-much-else-planned day and that&#8217;s what it&#8217;s been.  We slept in and then got started on laundry using the washer/dryer in our studio flat.  For lunch, though, we ventured out to explore more of the huge shopping center a few minutes walk way in Canary Wharf. One [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe title="2011 - London - Museum - around the city" width="960" height="540" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/InQcwVms6JU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<div style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a style="clear: left; float: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-right: 1em;" href="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-82.jpg"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-82-300x225.jpg" width="320" height="240" border="0" /></a></div>
<p>From the beginning we&#8217;ve planned to make Tuesday a laundry-and-not-much-else-planned day and that&#8217;s what it&#8217;s been.  We slept in and then got started on laundry using the washer/dryer in our studio flat.  For lunch, though, we ventured out to explore more of the huge shopping center a few minutes walk way in Canary Wharf.</p>
<p>One thing Jackie wanted to do was (I know this will amaze you) find the local library, called the &#8220;Idea Store.&#8221;  She looked it over and then we wandered through the mall before deciding to have some Thai food for lunch.  We had a nice rice/chicken/spices meal along with a couple of pots of tea.  It was quite good and filling.</p>
<p>After lunch we walked over the a community park that is situated right on the Thames.  There&#8217;s a very nice walkway along the river and we strolled there for awhile before returning to the flat to finish up laundry.</p>
<div style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;" href="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-59.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-59-300x225.jpg" width="320" height="240" border="0" /></a></div>
<p>I did considerable research in finding a place to stay in London.  It would be easy to spend a small fortune just on a hotel here.  Basically, the closer one stays to the main tourist areas around Buckingham, Hyde Park, etc. the more money it will cost.  However, if you are staying for a week or more, it&#8217;s worth the effort to find a flat to rent.  Generally speaking the flat will cost a bit more but will give you a lot more room and cooking capability which is nice for breakfast and maybe an occasional meal.  If you are willing to stay farther out, though, you can save some money.  I spent a lot of time on <a href="http://www.tripadvisor.com/">Tripadvisor</a> looking at reviews and found this place; outside the tourist area in, instead, the &#8220;Wall Street&#8221; of London.  The cost was about the same as a tiny room in a &#8220;city&#8221; hotel but the accommodations are much better.  One of the main things to think about when planning a London trip is that the tube gives you great access to everything.  If you are close to a tube station you&#8217;re never far from the rest of London.  By staying at Canary Wharf we&#8217;ve had easy access to a great shopping center with plenty of shops and restaurants plus easy access to the tube, the light rail, the river commuter services &#8211; all with Greenwich 10 minutes away one direction and the Tower of London 10 minutes away the other.</p>
<div style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a style="clear: left; float: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-right: 1em;" href="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-9-27-2011-9-00-25-AM.jpg"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-9-27-2011-9-00-25-AM-300x169.jpg" width="320" height="180" border="0" /></a></div>
<p>We&#8217;ve found the people of London to be always in a hurry, always polite, and always willing to help if you ask them.  We think they smoke too much and don&#8217;t like having to walk through a cloud of smoke around the doors of nearly every building.  Sometimes we&#8217;ve struggled to understand what they say and they&#8217;ve struggled to understand us.  We were surprised, though, at how many people there are speaking other languages.  It&#8217;s as common to hear people speaking other languages as it is to hear English.  We&#8217;ve seen many men in beards and turbans and women wearing veiled outfits.  Those people, by the way, have never made us feel uncomfortable in any way.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve seen less tattoos, more women wearing short skirts, and more men wearing dark suits with white shirts and black ties than we&#8217;ve seen at home.  Some of that may be due to being out here with all the business types.</p>
<div style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;" href="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-86.jpg"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/2011-London-86-225x300.jpg" width="240" height="320" border="0" /></a></div>
<p>We&#8217;ve been especially blessed by the weather.  It has been just terrific with lots of beautiful sunshine and unseasonably warm temperatures.  We came prepared for London&#8217;s fall weather and ended up enjoying the best of London&#8217;s summer weather instead.  The jackets have been left on the hangers and the umbrellas haven&#8217;t been carried.   If anyone asks us about late September/early October London weather we&#8217;ll tell them it&#8217;s some of the best in the world &#8212; of course Londoners will laugh us out of the room when we say it!</p>
<p>Thanks for reading.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
