<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>electricity &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/travel/tag/electricity/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/travel</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 18:46:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Project: Lasko 755320 Ceramic Tower</title>
		<link>/travel/2015/10/02/project-lasko-755320-ceramic-tower/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electricity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[product]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weather]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=1839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We have three options for heating our camper: The furnace &#8211; which is very inefficient but produces a lot of heat; runs on propane which we always pay for The heat pump &#8211; part of the air conditioning system but of limited use when the outside air is colder; runs on electricity which we may [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have three options for heating our camper:</p>
<ol>
<li>The furnace &#8211; which is very inefficient but produces a lot of heat; runs on propane which we always pay for</li>
<li>The heat pump &#8211; part of the air conditioning system but of limited use when the outside air is colder; runs on electricity which we may or may not pay for</li>
<li>A space heater &#8211; amount of heat depends on the unit; and, again, we may or may not pay for the electricity</li>
</ol>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QBI-XnowmC8/Vg7IZ0RHgpI/AAAAAAAAl4E/WuWOXVL1-dI/s144-o/100_4707.JPG"/> The past winters we have used a combination of the three.  However, in our case we generally spend the winter months in places where the electric service is part of the campsite, so using electric heat makes a lot of sense for us.  We&#8217;ve had  &#8220;cube&#8221; heaters that help a lot but still leave the 5th wheel feeling a bit drafty and with uneven heat.</p>
<p>On the RV forums I kept reading about the <strong>Lasko 755320 Ceramic Tower</strong> and how happy people are with it so we decided to give one a try.  You can find them at several retailers or online.  The tower has a digital readout, can be programmed, has a timer, and rotates.  It also comes with a remote control.  When we got ours it was 68 degrees in the camper &#8211; that running our little space heater and with the heat pump set on 72 and cycling on and off.  Within a half hour the Lasko had raised the temperature to 75.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m thinking we&#8217;ll remove the space heaters from service all together; although we may keep one as a backup and to supplement the heat on especially cold mornings.  At this point, I recommend this unit to RVers who are looking for alternative heating solutions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
