<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Grandchildren &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/travel/tag/grandchildren/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/travel</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 16:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sightseeing review: Columbus, TX</title>
		<link>/travel/2014/11/10/sightseeing-review-columbus-tx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 16:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Jackie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grandchildren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grandkids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[museum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sightseeing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=1138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Columbus, TX is a lovely town with a historic downtown with several historic homes and buildings. There&#8217;s plenty of shopping and all types of eating places. The town is divided between the I10 commercial area and the old town area. We happened to visit during the Folk Fest 2014. Two of the streets by the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="http://lh5.ggpht.com/-Zx0ooJJPY1k/VF6YXEoWhzI/AAAAAAAAhiU/j3B88sC4A7M/s144-c-o/100_3651.JPG"/>  Columbus, TX is a lovely town with a historic downtown with several historic homes and buildings. There&#8217;s plenty of shopping and all types of eating places.  The town is divided between the I10 commercial area and the old town area.  We happened to visit during the Folk Fest 2014. Two of the streets by the courthouse were blocked off and there were vendors selling crafts, clothes, food and other items. The funnel cakes were, as always, a big hit with me!  Our grandchildren, Sarah and Matthew, were fascinated by the glass blower at work. We could hear folk music being performed onstage as we walked and enjoyed the booths and looking inside the old Opera house. We toured the local museum which is located in the original water tower and fire house.  The Vintage car show was fun. We enjoyed seeing the work that had been done to make the classic cars look new again.  We especially enjoyed  going to the City park where a small military camp was set.  We chatted with the re-enactors there who told us about their weapons and uniforms.  We then watched a re-enactment of an 1836 battle between the Texas army and the Mexican army.  They shot off cannons and black powder guns giving us an idea of how the battle might have looked and sounded.  I always enjoy small town events and having our grandkids along made this one especially fun for us.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQVtI9EDjJ5ryml8HwBN4dMDyEkuW7jqx0vVfm1eZmBVULD-Flw7qvxM1gkpqgy0TO0Ah5GV3kMKTiS/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe><img decoding="async" src="/travel/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" />Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
