<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>LaGrange GA &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/lagrange-ga/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 12:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sabbatical Journey #3</title>
		<link>/2008/05/12/sabbatical-journey-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casita]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LaGrange GA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sabbatical leave]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/sabbatical-journey-3/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sunday started with a bang. Thunderstorms with plenty of wind swept through the area. There is a railroad right by the campground and right in the middle of the storm a train came through. Of course, we immediately thought of the stories about a tornado sounding like a train. Also, out on the highway some [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sunday started with a bang.  Thunderstorms with plenty of wind swept through the area.  There is a railroad right by the campground and right in the middle of the storm a train came through.  Of course, we immediately thought of the stories about a tornado sounding like a train.  Also, out on the highway some kind of emergency vehicle came through, at least twice, with sirens blaring.   The whole event cost us a couple of hours of sleep.  That along with the change to Eastern Time caused us to miss the early service at the nearby church.  We ended up hanging around till the 11:00 service at the Methodist church.  We were last in and first out, anxious to get on the road.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2008/05/P5123558.jpg"><img decoding="async" style="float:right;margin:0 0 10px 10px" src="/wp-content/uploads/2008/05/P5123558-300x225.jpg" border="0" /></a>The aftermath of the storms was clear skies but plenty of wind.  The little Casita camper tows like a dream and that remains true even in 30+ mph winds.  We crossed into North Carolina in good time and continued toward Creekwood Farm RV park near Waynesville.  Truthfully, I had debated stopping down the road a bit because of the very windy conditions.  Also, we drove back under clouds and spitting rain.  We arrived to 60 degrees with wind and rain but managed to get set up without getting too wet or cold.  Creekwood is a nice place.  Clean, and well ordered.  We got full hookups, and I mean full &#8211; including 70+ channels of cable TV!  Our little camper stayed warm and snug and we got our best night&#8217;s sleep of our short journey.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
