<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>projects &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//tag/projects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:48:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2021 &#8211; Project: new laminate floor</title>
		<link>//2021/04/28/2021-project-new-laminate-floor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Jackie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The carpet in our 2005 Safari Cheetah was original carpet. Also, some tiles needed attention so we decided to go with a cork back, waterproof laminate replacement. We did a similar project in 2015 in our 5th wheel so we knew a bit about the project. I did the work then, but these days I&#8217;m [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-R9msBpGxcCA/YIi-WQjozwI/AAAAAAABKAg/1oqwZK-KI40Lr28I1Mr6lQ39Ap8ejsaQgCPcBGAsYHg/s2046/IMG_20210425_183121-COLLAGE.jpg" width="1535" height="2046" class="aligncenter size-large" /></p>
<p>The carpet in our 2005 Safari Cheetah was original carpet.  Also, some tiles needed attention so we decided to go with a cork back, waterproof laminate replacement.  We did a <a href="//2015/01/14/project-installing-laminate-flooring-in-living-room/">similar project</a> in 2015 in our 5th wheel so we knew a bit about the project.  I did the work then, but these days I&#8217;m recovering from  arthroscopic knee surgery so it was easy to decide to pay someone to do the work.  We bought NuCore flooring from Floor and Decor.  Honestly, seeing how hard the guys worked taking out the old tile I don&#8217;t think I would have been able to do the job anyway.  In our motorhome, the tile sections (kitchen and bathroom mostly) were mounted on a second layer of pressed wood.  I think this was because the carpet was thicker than the tile.  They added a second pressed wood layer to lift the tile to match the carpet.  Some sections of tile came out as a unit.  The rest required breaking tile and tearing up the pressed wood.  </p>
<p>Also, our rig has four slides.  We decided to leave the carpet on the slides and tile in the bathroom.  The slides are full of furniture or cabinets that pretty much full the slides anyway.  This also simplified the project a bit &#8211; saving us on both material and labor.</p>
<p>The job is now complete and we&#8217;re pleased with the result.  As you can guess, the final chapter of the story can only be written after a few years of use.  For now, though, we are happy with our new floor.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vR5v6LCvUvnF_UI_njx1dmV1m0GKASdO2D25PsRLZMD4UHEZvel-o_oHNS_fxhXtYYNu6o6U_Hjntnt/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
