<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Wisconsin - Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/wisconsin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 23:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Campground Review: Holtwood Campground &#8211; Oconto, WI</title>
		<link>/2015/08/02/campground-review-holtwood-campground-oconto-wi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 20:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wisconsin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=1752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>﻿ Holtwood Campground in Oconto, WI is a popular seasonal campground with several sites for short term stays as well. It’s around 30 minutes north of Green Bay and was a good spot for us, giving us easy access to Green Bay but in a preferable small town setting. The campground is, I’d guess, around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/2015/08/02/campground-review-holtwood-campground-oconto-wi/">Campground Review: Holtwood Campground – Oconto, WI</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQ7wuUXusKhEu2Gex-3Wv36zUEl8UXgKRfQIrWzOtrEeBir6s-2P-BjxtOk4YWrLwp71PQa_QAG_pUm/embed?start=true&amp;loop=true&amp;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="960" height="569" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"><span data-mce-type="bookmark" style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span></iframe></p>
<p>Holtwood Campground in Oconto, WI is a popular seasonal campground with several sites for short term stays as well. It’s around 30 minutes north of Green Bay and was a good spot for us, giving us easy access to Green Bay but in a preferable small town setting. The campground is, I’d guess, around 60% seasonal sites and I was told that there’s a waiting list for those sites. Around the parameter, and right on Oconto River, is where most of the short term sites are. They are grass sites and set up so two RV’s share a common electric pedestal, with one rig facing the river and the other facing the road. This, though, isn’t always the case, as several sites are set up for “parallel parking” between the river and the road. The majority of the sites are full hook up with 50 amps although there are sections of the campground devoted to tent camping.</p>
<p>The river is a popular kayak/tubing spot and people also catch a variety of fish. Canoes, tubes, etc. are available for rent and firewood is for sale at the camp office. The city pool and ball fields plus a disc golf course is nearby.</p>
<p>Our site was situated in an interesting spot. We were right on the river, a pretty spot. However, just across the river is a Kwik-Trip convenience store, a mini-golf course, McDonalds, and auto parts store. However, to get to these, and other stores, at least without a boat, we had to drive out of the campground and around it through town, following the river. The driving distance was over a mile and a half. There’s talk about adding a foot bridge, which would be convenient. However, many of the seasonal residents are concerned with the amount of non-camping foot traffic through the campground that would result.</p>
<p>The campground recommends reservations, and I’m sure they are needed on summer weekends as many folks from Green Bay come for a quick get-away. We had good 4G Verizon and got two of our three Dish Network satellites. I think it would be easy enough to get all the satellites in some sites and downright impossible to get any of them in others. All in all, we really like this campground and will likely return on future trips into and through northeast Wisconsin.</p><p>The post <a href="/2015/08/02/campground-review-holtwood-campground-oconto-wi/">Campground Review: Holtwood Campground – Oconto, WI</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
