<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Kentucky &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/kentucky/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:56:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2017 &#8211; Campground Review: Fort Boonesborough State Park, KY</title>
		<link>/2017/05/10/2017-campground-review-fort-boonesborough-state-park-ky/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 19:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kentucky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[museum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[state park]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=2307</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our stay at Fort Boonesborough State Park near Lexington, KY was a short but enjoyable one. The roads in this large campground are good and the sites are all paved. The campground has 161 sites. All have electric and water but only 18 of them are full hookup. Be sure to pay attention when making [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="separator" style="clear: both;"><a href="https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEi6Z4hrFT7inogj1jsoISWrwNU7Nj-b9CYavU0ZOTPUFgsGtXgzXZcwRXvbEL5GVSqNfKvG-TkLv8oJ7ZtDSJc8YLFDbvwxclufBb-Sl5iJB0lux3J9A4gQ3jBEti1yThoc4bbWQbS0SDm7t6yJP3HoRJPwRdFSgfhDd7eksj1WzhRlL2kvB6v5ftz4dDP7/s1600/20170508_160026.jpg" style="display: block; padding: 1em 0; text-align: center; "><img decoding="async" alt="" border="0" data-original-height="1536" data-original-width="2048" src="https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEi6Z4hrFT7inogj1jsoISWrwNU7Nj-b9CYavU0ZOTPUFgsGtXgzXZcwRXvbEL5GVSqNfKvG-TkLv8oJ7ZtDSJc8YLFDbvwxclufBb-Sl5iJB0lux3J9A4gQ3jBEti1yThoc4bbWQbS0SDm7t6yJP3HoRJPwRdFSgfhDd7eksj1WzhRlL2kvB6v5ftz4dDP7/s1600/20170508_160026.jpg"/></a></div>
<p>Our stay at Fort Boonesborough State Park near Lexington, KY was a short but enjoyable one. The roads in this large campground are good and the sites are all paved. The campground has 161 sites. All have electric and water but only 18 of them are full hookup. Be sure to pay attention when making reservations if you want full hookups. The water hookups are shared between every other site and some of them are a long way from the campsite. I ended up getting out some hoses I haven’t used in a while to reach our spigot.</p>
<p>The road you turn on to get to the campground is at the bottom of a “trucks use lower gear” hill just before the Kentucky River Bridge. You will want to keep your speed down to make the turn onto Hwy 388 to get to the campground. Also, about half way down that same steep hill is the turn off for the Fort itself. You don’t want that first turn, but rather, Hwy 388. It is all pretty straightforward once you are actually arriving but, again, be ready for that steep downhill just prior to turning off to the campground.</p>
<p>While there is plenty of space between the individual campsites you might want to be aware that the back in sites aren’t all deep enough for a larger RV. Also, if the campsite description says the slope is moderate or severe you can believe it. Some of the sites are pretty steep. Again, be sure to read the site description when making reservations.</p>
<p> Of course, the reason for this state park is that this is the location of Fort Boonesborough which was constructed in 1775 by Daniel Boone and those he lead.  Today the recreated fort is a living history museum.  We thoroughly enjoyed looking around, watching an informative film, and especially chatting with the folks who gave us a glimpse into life at the fort.  We think the fort is well worth the time and modest entry fee and highly recommend it to all traveling through this Kentucky bluegrass country.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTXGOUWJpX07zOUzYSW9AN_yw7x4RTRczjn-duqEWCL2mEdlCtRFq1BB6WBE2GEuOfc6Kea3x6WVkUH/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" />Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
