<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mississippi &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/travel/tag/mississippi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/travel</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:31:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; Shortstop: Roosevelt State Park, Morton, MS</title>
		<link>/travel/2019/05/01/2019-shortstop-roosevelt-state-park-morton-ms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mississippi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shortstop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[state park]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=3824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We spent a few extra days in Jackson, MS waiting to get into a shop that does front end alignment service on bigger motorhomes. I wanted to use this particular shop because the owner has a motorhome very similar to ours and also he gets great reviews. I think we made the right choice and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail" src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-uNgLQPnH0hM/XMpGSTC-8HI/AAAAAAAA7Bw/8Y6KgaSc27Y4e7YwoahIbKhbKgailXZkwCKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20190501_191304.jpg" width="1600" height="900" />We spent a few extra days in Jackson, MS waiting to get into a shop that does front end alignment service on bigger motorhomes. I wanted to use this particular shop because the owner has a motorhome very similar to ours and also he gets great reviews. I think we made the right choice and recommend Shipp&#8217;s Truck Specialist in Florence. However, the 3-4 hour job turned into a 2 day job. We spent one night in the shop parking lot. They finished on Wednesday at about 5:00 and we wanted to find a spot with hookups for the night before getting back on the road again the next morning.</p>
<p>Roosevelt State Park in Moran, MS is just a few miles east of Jackson so we decided to go there. The entrance to the park is very close to I20. The &#8220;new&#8221; campgrounds, though, are a couple of miles in. The road is about a lane and a half wide, with lots of twists and turns. We didn&#8217;t meet anyone coming in – won&#8217;t be able to report on our exit till tomorrow. If we meet another motorhome it will be a tight squeeze.</p>
<p>The state park features a pretty lake with a big water slide that must delight the kids. There are cabins, a motel, and other nice facilities. The park hosts various community events throughout the year.</p>
<p>The roads in the campground are just one lane with no shoulders. Many of the sites are too short for us at 39&#8242;. I was also concerned about being able to make the turns in and out of the sites while keeping the front and back tires on pavement. There are some premium sites right on the lake that look inviting. I eased through the campground looking for the right combination of level + long enough + reasonable back in/pull out. It took a few minutes but I found a nice spot across from the bathhouse parking lot and backed in. Site 73 is just right for us and, in spite of the many sites that slope, this spot is nicely level.  There is no room for the car but the parking lot across the road is fine.</p>
<p>I can see that locals who get to know this campground really like it. However, for an overnight stay the long narrow drive in and the even narrower campground roads with ditches making it a challenge to make some of the turns make this State Park a less than desirable short stop of us. For a longer stay it might be worth it though.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSac2vcY7S4YnVJueFZrxu6OxdEmOhkvOTrqYlVri3Ua2OUFb1HO5yk_AqMsTv-CUxE-Z7UqMR5nXwQ/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" src="/travel/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
