<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Missouri &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/travel/tag/missouri/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/travel</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 21:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; Beagle Bay RV Park &#8211; Sarcoxie, MO</title>
		<link>/travel/2019/10/09/2019-beagle-bay-rv-park-sarcoxie-mo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 21:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Missouri]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We were invited to serve as speakers for a series of services at Mt Vernon, MO Church of the Nazarene and this RV park is right down I44 from the church. First, I&#8217;ll tell you the good things about this campground. It is very convenient to the interstate. The sites are all pull-through, full hookup, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-smqzJliMFVo/XZ5Oq-5XqSI/AAAAAAABB5w/BffXc9YNYDUHJwHw_mJGQuMvqqOznobawCKgBGAsYHg/s1600/IMG_20191004_184522.jpg" width="1600" height="902" class="aligncenter size-large" /><br />
We were invited to serve as speakers for a series of services at Mt Vernon, MO Church of the Nazarene and this RV park is right down I44 from the church.  First, I&#8217;ll tell you the good things about this campground.  It is very convenient to the interstate.  The sites are all pull-through, full hookup, and (I think) all 50 amp.  The roads and sites are pretty good gravel surface.  Most sites are reasonably level.  There&#8217;s a pool that appears to be maintained, although it was unused during our October stay.  There&#8217;s a laundry that seems to get plenty of use.  I had a clear view of the sky for the eastern Dish satellites although the shady sites would likely make it difficult if not impossible to get satellite TV from many of the sites.  Our Verizon signal was solid.  One unique feature of the campground is that nearly every site has porch swings installed.  </p>
<p>The close proximity to the interstate is both a good and a bad thing.  The sound of traffic never ceases.  After a while you tend to tune it out, but, of course, the closer you are to the front of the campground the louder it is.  It appeared to me that overnight guests were generally put in sites that put the main building between them and the interstate &#8211; a wise move. The campground, in general, just feels tired.  I saw a worker painting and, honestly, there&#8217;s a lot of painting needed.  The bathrooms were clean enough but had a funky smell &#8211; a mixture of old plus musty.  </p>
<p>Several sites are occupied by longer term residents &#8211; mostly working people who get up every morning and return in the evenings.  Their campsites are generally orderly and we had no negative impression of them at all.  The campground workers were friendly and helpful.  </p>
<p>Most travelers stop off just for an overnight and this campground is quite suitable for that: right on the interstate, pull through sites, easy in and out. This is far from our favorite campground, but we&#8217;d stay at it again without any hesitation.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSW0FE6lpagQ28cO22NeNowJsr7Ag0YtwUek0HhrgmCo5qm0Jw9LoqEsOLGgCrtkjnCYS7NyGnGabS1/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" src="/travel/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
