<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>camping &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//tag/camping/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:17:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Reflecting on our 2021 Adventure</title>
		<link>//2021/12/28/reflecting-on-our-2021-adventure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fulltime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4846</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our 2021 Adventure kept us in Texas for the year – our first full year in one state since we began the fulltime RV life. A combination of Covid concerns, other health issues, and time serving churches as interim pastor kept us in our home state for the year. We started the year in Denison, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><figure id="attachment_4847" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4847" style="width: 960px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="//wp-content/uploads/2021/12/IMG_20210803_102115-1024x576.jpg" alt="" width="960" height="540" class="size-large wp-image-4847" srcset="//wp-content/uploads/2021/12/IMG_20210803_102115-1024x576.jpg 1024w, //wp-content/uploads/2021/12/IMG_20210803_102115-300x169.jpg 300w, //wp-content/uploads/2021/12/IMG_20210803_102115-768x432.jpg 768w, //wp-content/uploads/2021/12/IMG_20210803_102115-1536x864.jpg 1536w, //wp-content/uploads/2021/12/IMG_20210803_102115.jpg 1913w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-4847" class="wp-caption-text">2021 &#8211; Medina Lake Thousand Trails &#8211; Lakehills, TX</figcaption></figure><br />
Our 2021 Adventure kept us in Texas for the year – our first full year in one state since we began the fulltime RV life.  A combination of Covid concerns, other health issues, and time serving churches as interim pastor kept us in our home state for the year.</p>
<p>We started the year in Denison, TX serving as interim pastor.  North Texas isn&#8217;t the greatest place to be in an RV in the winter but serving a great congregation of people made up for the cold and windy days.  We finished up and headed south just as the infamous Texas February freeze began.  Waiting out freezing rain and slick roads kept us at one place a few extra days, then a break in the weather allowed us to make a run for Lake Conroe Thousand Trails before the real deep freeze and snow came.   We were very thankful for our generator when much of Texas lost power.  We stayed comfortable, but homebound, waiting for &#8220;spring&#8221; just a week or so later.</p>
<p>Our winter stay at Green Caye in Dickinson, TX was extended due to some health issues and by the time we were ready to travel it was already early summer.  We decided to work our way to the beautiful Texas Hill Country (north and west of San Antonio).  The Texas summer heat was no fun, but the lower humidity of that area did help.  While we were there I was asked to fill in at a church in Devine, TX.  This is a small congregation of good people and it was a pleasure to minister to them.</p>
<p>As summer ended we began to reverse our course staying at the three area Thousand Trails before landing back at Green Caye to end the year and begin the New Year.</p>
<p>One of the great things about being retired fulltime RVers is the absolute flexibility we enjoy.  It&#8217;s easy to adjust our plans when desired or needed.  This has been a year of adjustments.  </p>
<p>We had one big repair this year &#8211; a black water tank leak (yuck!).  While the motorhome was in the shop we stayed in a Thousand Trails cabin for nearly two weeks.  Fortunately, we get one week a year in a cabin at no cost and a discount the rest of the time.  The repair was, though, expensive.  It was also necessary and we are thankful that we haven&#8217;t had any more issues.  </p>
<p>We&#8217;re thinking 2022 is going to be a new chapter in our retirement adventure.  Exactly what is still being decided.  Stay tuned! </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
