<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ohio &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/travel/tag/ohio/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/travel</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 16:05:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; Sightseeing Along Lake Erie in N.E. Ohio</title>
		<link>/travel/2019/09/07/2019-sightseeing-along-lake-erie-in-n-e-ohio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 16:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Jackie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[museum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Park]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nature]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ohio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sightseeing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our stay in northeastern Ohio was a longer stay for us and that gave us plenty of time to explore the area. We never get our fill of waterfalls so even though we hiked Watkins Glen and then visited Niagara Falls over the past few weeks, we took a day trip and visited a couple [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-yByPuzIMN14/XXPUgVjHU8I/AAAAAAABBAM/63cVznUHtg09yCqamTIp58hY5bSyBQ5WACKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20190905_130252.jpg" width="1600" height="961" class="aligncenter size-large" /><br />
Our stay in northeastern Ohio was a longer stay for us and that gave us plenty of time to explore the area.</p>
<p>We never get our fill of waterfalls so even though we hiked Watkins Glen and then visited Niagara Falls over the past few weeks, we took a day trip and visited a couple more waterfalls near Cleveland OH.  <strong>Chagrin Falls</strong>, just south of Cleveland is located in the town of Chagrin. There are cute shops and restaurants around it. It is obviously a destination for people wanting to get out of the big city and although not overwhelming the falls are pretty and a nice place to eat lunch or just hang out. From there we drove through the country and arrived at the <strong>Brandywine Falls</strong> in beautiful <strong>Cayahoga Valley National Park</strong>. The falls have hiking and biking trails.  We walked down a boardwalk for a great view of the falls. It is beautiful and well worth the effort to get down there and back. There is also an overlook for people who cannot or choose to not take the stairs.</p>
<p>On the Saturday before Labor Day We drove to <strong>Geneva-On-The-Lake</strong> and found it very busy due to a variety of events happening that day. We especially enjoyed a big Volkswagen car show in the city park which was filled with VWs and camper vans from across the years. Afterward, we enjoyed sitting on a bench and listening to the waves of Lake Erie for a while.</p>
<p>We went to Cleveland to visit the Historic William G. Matthew steam ship but found that it was only open on weekends after Labor Day. The ship is adjacent to the <strong>Rock N Roll Hall of Fame</strong> and since we were already there so we thought we would check it out. Honestly, since we aren’t fans of current popular music our expectations weren&#8217;t very high but there was more of interest to us than we expected.  We spent most of our time in the sections of the museum that focus on the early days of rock and roll music.  We heard lots of music and watched clips of singers from the 40&#8217;s, 50&#8217;s and 60&#8217;s. We saw photos, costumes and other memorabilia from many singers and groups. It was interesting seeing displays of groups like The Beach Boys, the Beatles, and the Temptations. Other singers included Elvis Presley, Roy Orbison, Aretha Franklin, Johnny Cash and many more. We were able to walk through the tour bus that was built for Johnny and June Cash and their son. Interesting and sobering to us was the way the music changed to darker, angry, themes as time passed.</p>
<p>There is a historically unique restaurant near our campground: <strong>Covered Bridge Pizza</strong> in North Kingsville. The dining area is inside a covered bridge. The bridge was originally the Foreman Road Bridge built in 1862. In 1972 the county decided to replace it and the old bridge was sold for five dollars! It was carefully dismantled and placed in storage. In 1975 half of the old bridge was used to open the restaurant we visited and in 1977 a second location was opened using the other half of the bridge. There are a variety of items on the menu but we were there for pizza. The crust is made fresh daily and the spicy sauce along with the meat and cheese made an excellent lunch.</p>
<p>On a clear sunny day we took a picnic and visited a few of the many <strong>parks along Lake Erie</strong>. It was fun seeing the various parks. One was small with few picnic tables and small playground. Another had a large covered area with tables and a concession with boardwalks down to the beach. Yet another had a covered area with tables and several porch type swings with the beach area adjacent to it. We had a pleasant lunch by carrying our lunch and chairs down close to the water. A nice quiet way to spend a few hours.</p>
<p>When we saw advertising about a <strong>balloon glow</strong> not far from our campground we decided to go. There were eight of the giant hot air balloons that were beautiful when lit up.  There were a lot of people there enjoying the display.  The business, Debonné, hosts a full scale hot air balloon festival in the spring, it must be amazing to see.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTxKDw3J2kNLv8ew5hlbVeUzo9yIlTH17SAw-zbCzE6i_3CBpqVNb15k0pN3E7JxC3hSdpRqrUf76d7/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" src="/travel/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
