<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>fulltime &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/fulltime/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 21:11:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Winding down our fulltime RV Adventure</title>
		<link>/2022/07/16/winding-down-our-fulltime-rv-adventure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 21:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fulltime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[planning]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We started our fulltime RV adventure over 9 years ago in May of 2013. Our travels have taken us across the USA, coast to coast, and we have thoroughly enjoyed the journey. The past couple of years brought some major changes to our lifestyle. For one thing, COVID cramped our style the same as it [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_4879" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4879" style="width: 800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-4879 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IMG_20210824_203057-1.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="450" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IMG_20210824_203057-1.jpg 800w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IMG_20210824_203057-1-300x169.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IMG_20210824_203057-1-768x432.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-4879" class="wp-caption-text">2021 &#8211; Old River Rd RV &#8211; Kerrville, TX</figcaption></figure>
<p>We started our fulltime RV adventure over 9 years ago in May of 2013. Our travels have taken us across the USA, coast to coast, and we have thoroughly enjoyed the journey. The past couple of years brought some major changes to our lifestyle.</p>
<ol>
<li>For one thing, <strong>COVID</strong> cramped our style the same as it did for everyone else. We hunkered down in a comfortable urban campground for the duration.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, I kept getting requests to serve as <strong>interim pastor</strong> in different places. What with COVID making it difficult to plan and the satisfaction we get from helping churches, we took the departure from our touring lifestyle in stride and enjoyed ministering to some wonderful people.</li>
<li>Also, <strong>medical stuff</strong> has occupied more and more of our calendar. Thank God, the concerns haven&#8217;t been major. They have, though, impacted our travel plans as well as our bank account!</li>
<li>While we full well know that there&#8217;s a lot to see and do in this country, we&#8217;ve had a bit of a feeling of <strong>&#8220;been-there-done-that.&#8221;</strong> There are many gaps in our travel, but we&#8217;ve seen a great deal over the past several years and have visited some favorite areas more than once.</li>
<li>We&#8217;ve gotten kind of <strong>tired of living in a RV</strong>. I think this is related to slowing down our travel the past couple of years. Doing typical RV chores and living in a small space is well worth the inconvenience so long as the tradeoff is going places and seeing new things. For us, the less we have done, the less we have enjoyed the RV as a residence.</li>
<li>Finally, <strong>skyrocketing fuel costs</strong> have influenced our thinking. Fill ups costing hundreds of dollars do make one think twice about hitting the road.</li>
</ol>
<p>Had the slowdown not happened we might have continued the RV life a bit longer. You might say that we lost much of our &#8220;momentum&#8221; waiting out COVID, etc. Frankly, we never retired to <em>live</em> in a RV – rather we retired to <em>travel</em> in a RV.</p>
<p>All this to say we are retiring from fulltime RVing, at least for the foreseeable future. Even as I write this the motorhome is on a consignment lot waiting for the right buyer to come along. I expect to get a smaller rig at some point in the future so we can do some seasonal, short-term travel. Time will tell.</p>
<p>All of this, though, doesn&#8217;t mean our unconventional retirement adventures are over. In a few days we will begin an entirely new adventure. I&#8217;ll write more about that in a few days. We&#8217;re excited about this next step!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
