<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>television &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/television/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 04:36:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2018 &#8211; Project: Dish Tripod</title>
		<link>/2018/03/03/2018-project-dish-tripod/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 18:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[satellite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[upgrades]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=2713</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve written about my satellite TV setup before, mostly in reference to the Winegard Carryout I used for a few years. You can read those posts here. As I mentioned in the later reviews, I finally decided I was happier using a regular dish rather than the Carryout.  The reasons are in the final review [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve written about my satellite TV setup before, mostly in reference to the Winegard Carryout I used for a few years. You can <a href="/tag/satellite">read those posts here.</a></p>
<p>As I mentioned in the later reviews, I finally decided I was happier using a regular dish rather than the Carryout.  The reasons are in the final review so I won&#8217;t rehash them in this post.  All this to say that for the past few years I&#8217;ve used the home style dish and intend to keep on using it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-thumbnail alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-JupzI9TFMHE/WprjyfvkeKI/AAAAAAAAwd4/icgm6D_1YisUquTVkm7dufKlwD9CWtoawCCoYBhgL/s144-o/IMG_20180303_100148.jpg" width="144" height="81" />One of the weak links in this setup, though, was my tripod.  I inherited a small very basic one that is rather flimsy.  If the ground is unlevel, I put something under one leg to attempt to level it.  I also stake it out with guy wires to hold it steady in the wind.  It works but is far from an elegant solution.</p>
<p>I looked at the TV4RV tripod for some time.  However, it is pricy and I had a hard time pulling the trigger on it.  Finally, though, I went for it and I&#8217;m glad I did.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignleft " src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-1jkXB05SELg/Wy66UU-PtkI/AAAAAAAAzDA/FopuHdKIF8oiw_cr6tq8wfHim7U-fMvKgCKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20180303_111056.jpg" width="208" height="369" />The tripod is actually a modified surveyor&#8217;s tripod; each leg can be adjusted independently.  A compass is supplied that fits right into the top of the tripod, and you are supposed to aim the direction before you ever mount the dish onto the tripod. One key is getting it perfectly level, something that is easy enough to do using a simple bubble level and the individually adjustable legs. The other key is getting it tall enough to &#8220;look over&#8221; any trees, etc. that are in the line of sight to the satellites. In some locations the sky is clear and I just leave it low to the ground. In a few places, though, I need all the height I could get.</p>
<p>Generally, the whole setup is less than 15 minutes. <a href="/2019/08/29/using-a-home-style-dish/">I describe the process here.</a></p>
<p>You can anchor the tripod using a screw in doggie stake or, if the ground is rocky I just use a five gallon bucket of water. I think this is the Cadillac of portable dish tripods, and in spite of the cost, it&#8217;s a good investment for those of us who need to set up a home-style dish on a regular basis.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-HETS0t0syUo/WprjybtOmkI/AAAAAAAAwd4/15ZwzCCiMm8reITTAi-WVIAPRXGK7UJPQCCoYBhgL/s0/IMG_20180303_111115.jpg" width="1080" height="1920" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
