<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Virginia &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//tag/virginia/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 20:55:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; Harbor View Thousand Trails, Colonial Beach, VA</title>
		<link>//2019/06/26/2019-harbor-view-thousand-trails-colonial-beach-va/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 20:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virginia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=3917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We enjoyed our stay at Harbor View Thousand Trails in Colonial Beach, VA. This is a smaller Thousand Trails with only 144 or so sites. The campground is mostly level with decent spacing between the sites. However, campsites in much of the campground are &#8220;back to back.&#8221; There is room between sites, but the neighbor [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-d2DGIZD3XkY/XRPaYLLzg0I/AAAAAAAA8oU/gPZjYQuWkW0KMKpRQ1jc4KM9CqB8jUIoQCKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20190612_103037.jpg" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail" /><br />
We enjoyed our stay at Harbor View Thousand Trails in Colonial Beach, VA.  This is a smaller Thousand Trails with only 144 or so sites.  The campground is mostly level with decent spacing between the sites.  However, campsites in much of the campground are &#8220;back to back.&#8221;  There is room between sites, but the neighbor to the back will practically be bumper to bumper.  I will mention that there are a few pull through sites and also some tent sites.</p>
<p>This is one of the Thousand Trails campgrounds that have started assigning spots based on rig size.  We were led to our site by an employee on a golf cart.  The site was, indeed, suitable for us.  During the week there were a few vacant sites, but things pretty much filled up on the weekends.</p>
<p>The campground features a large pool, a basketball court with a new playing surface, and a mini-golf course which was being redone during our stay.  From what I could tell the campsites are all 50 amp/FHU sites.</p>
<p>The place has lots of tree cover providing welcome shade on hot, humid afternoons.  It also makes it practically impossible to get a satellite signal.  It looked to me like the seasonals have chosen a few spots that offer a &#8220;hole in the sky&#8221; for satellite.  I used all my satellite finding skill to spot one of the Dish Network satellites.  We didn&#8217;t get most of the channels we usually get but we got the baseball games we enjoy and that worked out for us.</p>
<p>The nearest Walmart is nearly 30 minutes away but Colonial Beach has a couple of grocery stores and plenty of eating places.  There are lots of historic attractions in the area and we enjoyed visiting several of them.</p>
<p>Harbor View doesn&#8217;t really offer a view of any harbor.  There&#8217;s a marina adjacent to the property on Mattox Creek but it isn&#8217;t associated with the campground.  No campsite has a view of even the creek although a few are close to a small fishing pond located in the campground.  My Verizon signal was quite good giving us solid data service.  </p>
<p>All in all, Harbor View is a nice place and worth adding to your Thousand Trails camping plans.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQ18WYi7VQcgmGgYNSGtsnNmvUGKXV8lRYGpWXryT5NzcnE7hquTJHrZNI_q3Q9aDswMRraIZxsLmUw/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" src="//wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
