<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Escapees &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/escapees/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:42:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2017 &#8211; Campground Review: Raccoon Valley Escapees, Heiskell, TN</title>
		<link>/2017/05/07/2017-campground-review-raccoon-valley-escapees-heiskell-tn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 22:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Escapees]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fulltime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennessee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=2298</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We’re just finishing up a one month stay at Raccoon Valley Escapees RV Park at Heiskell, TN, just north of Knoxville. The setting of the park is scenic, in a pretty valley with tree covered ridges on either side. Of course, this is eastern Tennessee, home of the stunning Smoky Mountains. Without doubt, this is [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="separator" style="clear: both;"><a href="https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEj0z_KDK9osMpAaQ29I6fS6LYX78dL35TMVgf-Vo61orRxHZkxZmJqK6t2NkpFQuKitoSSll8QcLxVFPLTR0fVp3feeCnPhN8JTD6O_Kr2eFJAU8hnBWiOsoxhLORQMqEfHVG6EZPYnZ3WRsbwKcxPFr8EuBCGM9NaxcbZHODDvQJaGraviMeRY5k9PQg2U/s1600/IMG_5304.JPG" style="display: block; padding: 1em 0; text-align: center; "><img decoding="async" alt="" border="0" data-original-height="2448" data-original-width="3264" src="https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEj0z_KDK9osMpAaQ29I6fS6LYX78dL35TMVgf-Vo61orRxHZkxZmJqK6t2NkpFQuKitoSSll8QcLxVFPLTR0fVp3feeCnPhN8JTD6O_Kr2eFJAU8hnBWiOsoxhLORQMqEfHVG6EZPYnZ3WRsbwKcxPFr8EuBCGM9NaxcbZHODDvQJaGraviMeRY5k9PQg2U/s1600/IMG_5304.JPG"/></a></div>
<p> We’re just finishing up a one month stay at Raccoon Valley Escapees RV Park at Heiskell, TN, just north of Knoxville. The setting of the park is scenic, in a pretty valley with tree covered ridges on either side. Of course, this is eastern Tennessee, home of the stunning Smoky Mountains. Without doubt, this is a great area. The campground itself is basically a gravel parking lot. Sites are very close to one another with one’s neighbor’s utilities in your front yard. The grounds are well kept, the rest rooms clean, and there’s a nice activity center.</p>
<p>The campground hosts a weekly gathering of local musicians who sing and play for a few hours each week. Anyone who plays an acoustical instrument is welcome to join in. The music ranges from pretty good to “not pretty good” (if you get my drift.) However, everyone is having a good time and it makes for a friendly, easy going evening.</p>
<p>The monthly prices here are quite good and that has drawn a variety of residents. There are traditional Escapees who travel in their RV’s full time and there are working people who had never heard of Escapees, but joined to get the discount rate as residents of this park. Most everyone is friendly or at least cordial. Because of price, location, and limited sites the park stays pretty busy.</p>
<p>My Verizon signal was good. Our satellite TV is via Dish Network. There are plenty of over-the-air TV stations but the primary Dish channels are on the Dish “eastern arc.” Since my dish is a western arc one, and since the trees pretty much blocked my western satellites I decided to bite the bullet and buy the replacement LNBs. I found them on Amazon for around $25. After swapping them out and aiming the dish to the eastern satellites I had all my channels again. From what research I’ve done, I’ll be using the eastern satellites for another month or two and in the future I’m sure I’ll be glad to have the option of switching between satellite sets when we travel east.</p>
<p>Honestly, a month was too long for us to be at this park. Had the campsites had a bit more elbow room we would have liked it better but it still would have been longer than we really wanted. I’d return here for a week or maybe two, but that’s about it.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQgS9yETaHydBLHF1-DAgFpdYaTWft_Z8ScSnMehiOasSb2Dykl51zLdhoX75haGjDoZKj2wEs4dC-O/embed?start=true&amp;loop=true&amp;delayms=3000" width="480" height="299" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" />Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
