<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>generators &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/generators/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 22:21:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hurricane Ike &#8211; 20: Give me power!</title>
		<link>/2008/09/23/hurricane-ike-20-give-me-power/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electricity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[generators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hurricane Ike]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[observations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weather]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/hurricane-ike-20-give-me-power/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I write this on Tuesday morning &#8211; day 10 and counting without electricity at our house. We are thankful for the loan of a 5kw generator which we are using to power our camper with a/c. I&#8217;m having to buy around $20 in gas a day just to run it in the evenings and overnight. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I write this on Tuesday morning &#8211; day 10 and counting without electricity at our house. We are thankful for the loan of a 5kw generator which we are using to power our camper with a/c. I&#8217;m having to buy around $20 in gas a day just to run it in the evenings and overnight. It&#8217;s not to high a price to be able to sleep, something that would be hard to do otherwise. Our overnight lows have been in the mid 70&#8217;s the past few nights with high humidity. I think we have a minor cool front coming in tomorrow. It will drop the temps a few degrees and is supposed to bring us some very welcome drier air.</p>
<p>Another complication is mosquitoes. They have exploded in number since the storm and being outside means constantly brushing them off or donating blood to their cause. Happily, the county has started aerial spraying. The sound of the &#8220;buzz bombers&#8221; was welcome this morning and I was actually able to sit on the back patio to read my Bible at the start of my day.</p>
<p>One of the biggest problems for Jackie is that she has to go through several intersections where the stop and go lights are either not working or not there at all. In morning rush hour traffic that turns into a nightmare with traffic backing up at some spots as far as you can see. Also, people tend to get a little nutso about stuff like that.</p>
<p><a href="/2008/09/18/hurricane-ike-6-the-morning-after/">Lots of photos here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
