<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rhapsody of the Seas - Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/rhapsody-of-the-seas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2009 &#8211; Cruising to Alaska &#8211; Downtown Seattle</title>
		<link>/2009/08/24/cruising-to-alaska-august-22-2009-downtown-seattle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alaska]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cruising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Library]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rhapsody of the Seas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Seattle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sightseeing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Washington]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/cruising-to-alaska-august-22-2009-downtown-seattle/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We spent our last vacation day exploring downtown Seattle. Jackie especially wanted to visit the Seattle Central Library which is famous for its design and unique architecture. We arrived just in time to join an architect led tour of the library. It was quite interesting and I recommend the tour to anyone. We, and about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/2009/08/24/cruising-to-alaska-august-22-2009-downtown-seattle/">2009 – Cruising to Alaska – Downtown Seattle</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe title="2009 - Downtown Seattle, Library, Market" width="960" height="540" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pAXpIzDzU94?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>We spent our last vacation day exploring downtown Seattle. Jackie especially wanted to visit the Seattle Central Library which is famous for its design and unique architecture. We arrived just in time to join an architect led tour of the library. It was quite interesting and I recommend the tour to anyone.</p>
<p>We, and about every person in the Seattle metro area headed for Pike Place. It was packed. Still, we enjoyed checking out all the flower and fish and vegetable venders. We also had lunch at a crowded and busy little fish and chips place. After an hour or so at Pike Place we headed up the hill and bought some coffee and sat down for a nice break.</p>
<p>All the downtown area is a free ride zone on the city bus system, so we hopped on and off at several places before boarding the monorail to City Center where we watched a street performer doing some nifty juggling.</p>
<p>We finished off the evening at the Cheesecake Factory. Neither of us could eat all the food that we ordered. From there it was back to the hotel for final packing in preparation for an early flight home.</p><p>The post <a href="/2009/08/24/cruising-to-alaska-august-22-2009-downtown-seattle/">2009 – Cruising to Alaska – Downtown Seattle</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
