<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>internet &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/internet/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 23:46:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2018 &#8211; Cedar Lake, IN Ministries RV Park</title>
		<link>/2018/06/03/2018-cedar-lake-in-ministries-rv-park/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 23:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indiana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=2996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cedar Lake Ministries, located about an hour southeast of Chicago in northwestern Indiana, has roots reaching back over 100 years when Chicago&#8217;s Moody Church took over management of a railroad recreation destination on a large lake. The ministry at this retreat center continues to this day. The Center has a nice RV park that is [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Zv81EXvgVUY/WxR7nxQ-AgI/AAAAAAAAyFY/sEcqk30KRwoBYf29XVruOMo3jsVfwsZBACKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20180530_201434.jpg" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail" />Cedar Lake Ministries, located about an hour southeast of Chicago in northwestern Indiana, has roots reaching back over 100 years when Chicago&#8217;s Moody Church took over management of a railroad recreation destination on a large lake.  The ministry at this retreat center continues to this day.  The Center has a nice RV park that is open to the public and that is where we have been the past few days.  The RV park offers FHU back in sites, some with 50 amp electric service.  The sites aren&#8217;t especially deep, but there is adequate parking for extra vehicles.  The bathhouse is nicely done and clean.  Water spigots are on shared hookups between every other site, equally unhandy to those on both sides so extra water hose will likely be needed.  WiFi was pretty good although we did get frequent drops requiring us to reconnect.  The sites on the north side of the road in and out are most likely to be satellite friendly.  While we were at the campground there was a Christian music concert that we were welcome to attend.  We thought the music was pretty good.  There is no direct lake access but it is just a short walk to the public portion of the retreat center where there are benches along the lake, affording us nice views.  My Verizon signal was good.  We give this retreat center campground two thumbs up and would happily return.</p>
<p><center><iframe width="504" height="284" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/re25hJLgySA" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" />Click this for full screen photos<br />
<a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/f94AlXMbIfr8Tng93">See individual photos with captions here.</a> </center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
