<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>North Carolina &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//tag/north-carolina/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 01:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; Shortstop: Holly Point Campground &#8211; Wake Forest, NC</title>
		<link>//2019/05/23/2019-shortstop-holly-point-campground-wake-forest-nc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 01:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Carolina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shortstop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[state park]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=3864</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our one night stop at Holly Point Campground in Wake Forest, NC was an unplanned one and it came just in front of one of the hardest weekends of the year to find a campsite: Memorial Day weekend. Our motorhome was scheduled for a front windshield replacement in Winston-Salem (following my run-in with a tree [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-_ZXjl5NkIa4/XOdC3eXi71I/AAAAAAAA7pQ/IFrNXAZcvy4V3w9T-SIGBg-UHFx9vi-JACKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20190523_192214.jpg" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail" /><br />
Our one night stop at Holly Point Campground in Wake Forest, NC was an unplanned one and it came just in front of one of the hardest weekends of the year to find a campsite: Memorial Day weekend.</p>
<p>Our motorhome was scheduled for a front windshield replacement in Winston-Salem (following my run-in with a tree in South Carolina). The replacement took longer than I had anticipated and by the time we were ready to travel it was too late to make the longer drive we had planned.</p>
<p>While we were waiting on the windshield repair I was searching the internet for a suitable spot for one night. This campground gets good reviews and, even though it is booked up starting Friday, we were able to pick from several vacant spots for a Thursday one night stay.</p>
<p>Honestly, I wanted to find an &#8220;interstate campground&#8221; that caters to people just wanting to stop for a night, but came up empty on my search. Holly Point is farther from I85 than I wanted for just a one nighter, but (1) not finding a RV Park along the interstate and (2) it being the lead in to a holiday weekend I decided to go for it.</p>
<p>My biggest mistake, though, was the route I took from Durham. I left I85 onto Highway 70 and then traveled Highway 98 out to the Falls Lake Recreation area which is where Holly Point is located. Bad choice. There was construction and congestion the whole way, making for a tiring and slow conclusion to a long day. I&#8217;m not sure what route would be better, but this isn&#8217;t a good one.</p>
<p>Now, the campground is quite good. The sites are generally long with good spacing and reasonably level. They are 30 amp/water sites. The roads are paved and the sites are gravel. There&#8217;s a big lake. One of the highest compliments I can pay a campground is this: it reminds me of a Corps of Engineers campground.</p>
<p>My Verizon signal was good. Didn&#8217;t try to put the satellite up but I&#8217;m pretty sure I would have struck out at least from the site we picked.</p>
<p>Tell you what, it would, indeed, be a nice place to spend Memorial Day weekend.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQYwx8jMjaj9qoP7KpVF_N8wEaVC9bdd3ojtv_mizwiA3kuwjipag3r1OFnG2yvI4MwoJ1zg7QJP5im/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" src="//wp-content/uploads/2019/01/fullscreen-150x72.png" alt="" width="150" height="72" class="aligncenter size-thumbnail wp-image-3672" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Click this for full screen photos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
