<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>clean up &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//tag/clean-up/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 12:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hurricane Ike &#8211; 12: Neighbors</title>
		<link>//2008/09/18/hurricane-ike-12-neighbors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[clean up]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hurricane Ike]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/hurricane-ike-12-neighbors/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We were already well aware that we have good neighbors but this storm has really underscored that. Folks from up and down the block have come by to see if there is anything we need. The old greeting is “How are you?” The new greeting is, “Are you folks okay?” We’ve been asked that question [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="//wp-content/uploads/2008/09/P9134191.jpg"><img decoding="async" style="float:left;margin:0 10px 10px 0" src="//wp-content/uploads/2008/09/P9134191-300x225.jpg" border="0" /></a><br />We were already well aware that we have good neighbors but this storm has really underscored that.  Folks from up and down the block have come by to see if there is anything we need.  The old greeting is “How are you?”  The new greeting is, “Are you folks okay?”  We’ve been asked that question again and again.   One lady has repeatedly invited us over to eat.  She made breakfast tacos one morning and another good meal on Sunday evening.  Each time she comes by and says he made too much and wants us to come and eat.  As I have already mentioned, we were still seeing a little wind and rain from the storm and a couple of guys showed up to cut the huge fallen tree that was blocking our street.  Another neighbor borrowed my pruning saw and we borrowed his ladder.  A group of us got up this morning and cleared the yard for another neighbor who evacuated for the storm.  We didn’t want them to come home to such a mess.</p>
<p><a href="https://plus.google.com/photos/101128941131953400860/albums/5246367878190115185">Lots of photos here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
