<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lake Conroe &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/lake-conroe/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:31:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2021 &#8211; Lake Conroe Thousand Trails &#8211; Willis, TX (Fall review)</title>
		<link>/2021/11/11/2021-lake-conroe-thousand-trails-willis-tx-fall-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fulltime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lake Conroe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4834</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We&#8217;ve had another good stay at Lake Conroe Thousand Trails, Willis, TX. As I posted a few months ago, we&#8217;ve stayed at this campground often and written plenty of reviews, so I&#8217;ll just share a few random thoughts about this property in this post. We think the best thing about Lake Conroe TT is the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/a/AVvXsEgJypld6gf65oTG6rtMFXbUH70tba9wDd2oOxOSHeDMfcBMO4krmWtD9GjhwjdVqYUzZxx78GBQsfA5RDJ_v7mkcZQ6k8HDYeGQaen6V3riHrtksaOlwGdp0VpAX0pC7EmRizB_Ft_0YgnLyAdrQz7Hpz6jGIywIPbhh_N5R9S-4QH_QNloYmZq_RaJWg=s4032" width="4032" height="2268" class="aligncenter size-large" /></p>
<p>We&#8217;ve had another good stay at Lake Conroe Thousand Trails, Willis, TX. As I posted a few months ago, we&#8217;ve stayed at this campground often and <a href="/tag/lake-conroe/">written plenty of reviews</a>, so I&#8217;ll just share a few random thoughts about this property in this post.</p>
<p>We think the best thing about Lake Conroe TT is the gorgeous sunsets over the lake. A lot of people head down to the boat launch to enjoy to view. However, if you want the best view walk down to the lake front in &#8220;The Reserve&#8221; – that&#8217;s the permanent community just to the left at the entrance gate. You get a terrific sunset view there.</p>
<p>When all the new sites were added to the right of the gate we felt that it freed up a lot of nice sites over in the older part of the campground. However, it seems that things have changed as more seasonal sites have been sold and the campground feels as full now as ever. That said, we&#8217;ve never had a problem finding a good spot to land. Upon our arrival this time we were told that there were only two or three sites open. However, when we started looking around we found two additional great spots to choose from.</p>
<p>Jackie really likes the big Kroger that is just a few minutes from the campground. It is built like Fred Meyers stores out on the west coast (same company). We think most people will find it worth visiting.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve been frustrated with the way many Thousand Trails handle packages &#8211; often charging as much as $5 a UPS/Fedex package.  It seems odd that a campground that is actively selling long term sites would treat their residents like that.  Anyway, you might want to know that there&#8217;s an Amazon Hub Locker just outside the gate at the RV Ranch.</p>
<p>Covid seems to have been the end of the on-site restaurant. However, the alternative is pretty good: food trucks set up on the property during busy times. Hopefully, they will sell enough food to make it worth their while to come out.</p>
<p>The Conroe area, in general is exploding in growth. Every time we come in to Lake Conroe after being out of the area it seems traffic is worse. I doubt it is going to get any better as housing development is going on everywhere. This area is being swallowed up by the city.</p>
<p>Another thing we have noticed is that there are more full time families in the campground. During the summers we don&#8217;t think much about how many children we see. However, now that school is in session we&#8217;ve been surprised at the large number of children in the campground during weekdays. I&#8217;ve seen the school bus making a stop at the gate, but it&#8217;s my impression that many of these children are being home schooled. I&#8217;m sure Covid has caused a major explosion in the number of children being home schooled. That, of course, fits right into the RV lifestyle. No judgement here, just something we have noticed.</p>
<p>We have always liked Lake Conroe Thousand Trails and rank it as one of the best in the system. I&#8217;m thinking that all the upgrades plus its location close to the big city plus the explosion of RVers is going to keep Lake Conroe running at near capacity most all the time. I suggest reserving as early as possible when planning on visiting this campground.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
