<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="//category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 01:16:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Fulltiming and the Coronavirus</title>
		<link>//2020/03/17/fulltiming-and-the-coronavirus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 01:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fulltime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[problems]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4538</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The coronavirus outbreak is a fluid situation.  Today&#8217;s guidance from officials may be outdated by this evening.  To some extent we are all just waiting for the next domino to fall.  Fulltime RVers aren&#8217;t exempt from all the uncertainty.  The other day I saw a meme on Facebook picturing a class C parked alone on [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><figure style="width: 1600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-xdSK9WHb0zw/XnATu6Kce5I/AAAAAAABECY/fHPdiOGfkR8fp_3wNPL5bZsfMJ2ju3dHACKgBGAsYHg/s1600/IMG_20191029_115537.jpg" width="1600" height="945" class="size-large" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">2019 &#8211; Airport Park CoE, Waco, TX</figcaption></figure><br />
The coronavirus outbreak is a fluid situation.  Today&#8217;s guidance from officials may be outdated by this evening.  To some extent we are all just waiting for the next domino to fall.  Fulltime RVers aren&#8217;t exempt from all the uncertainty.  The other day I saw a meme on Facebook picturing a class C parked alone on a peninsula overlooking a pretty lake.  The caption, meant to bring a smile, said that they were practicing social distancing.  Then, in less than a day I saw a news article that New Mexico was closing its campgrounds.  I couldn&#8217;t help but wonder if that RV was being evicted from that isolated spot.</p>
<p>I see that FMCA and Escapees have announced changes in their rally schedules.  No doubt that leaves some fulltimers looking for a place to land now that they won&#8217;t be attending their rally as planned.</p>
<p>In our case, we&#8217;re still at our winter campground.  In fact, we had already planned on a longer than usual stay while I serve as interim pastor at a local church during their pastoral search.  A few days ago I mentioned to the campground management that we just might be staying into the summer – not because of the church assignment but because our summer plans might be disrupted by the pandemic.</p>
<p>At this point I think fulltimers might be wise to find a campground they like that will allow longer stays.  Many of us are in the higher risk group and it makes sense to take advantage of our more unstructured lifestyle to land in an acceptable spot and wait for the storm to blow over.  Of course, everyone has their own particular concerns: family needs, events, appointments and the like.  If possible, though, I&#8217;d be looking into suitable long term parking.</p>
<p>And, while I&#8217;m writing, I&#8217;ll switch to my pastoral identity for a moment.  From a health point of view, we&#8217;re urged to wash our hands to protect against a virus infection.  From a spiritual point of view, I urge you to spend time with the Lord – maybe whispering a 20 second prayer each time you wash your hands – pray for our world and for ourselves and those we love.  Ask the Lord to protect you against the infection of fear and anxiety that is sweeping across the world.  Also, you might include a prayer of thanksgiving for running water and soap.  Oh yeah, also pray for our President and other national leaders; maybe health care providers and medical researchers too.</p>
<p>Come to think of it, you might need more than 20 seconds for those prayers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
