<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>nature &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/nature/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:14:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2023 &#8211; Tour of Isle of Skye, Scotland</title>
		<link>/2023/06/03/2023-tour-of-isle-of-skye-scotland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Jackie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nature]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scotland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sightseeing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=5133</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our tour from Inverness continued from Eilean Donan Castle across the bridge to the Isle of Skye. Skye is the largest of Scotland&#8217;s Inner Hebrides islands, around 50 miles north to south. It is known for its rugged landscapes and steep cliffs. Hikers and bikers love Skye and the bed and breakfasts are always booked [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe title="2023  - Tour of Isle of Skye, Scotland" width="960" height="540" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gQI_oiV6j4A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Our tour from Inverness continued from Eilean Donan Castle across the bridge to the Isle of Skye.  Skye is the largest of Scotland&#8217;s Inner Hebrides islands, around 50 miles north to south.  It is known for its rugged landscapes and steep cliffs.  Hikers and bikers love Skye and the bed and breakfasts are always booked well ahead of time.  We just happened to tour on a day with perfect weather – something that, we&#8217;re told, is no way promised.  We saw the Old Man of Storr, a famous rock formation.  Supposedly, it looks like a man lying on his back looking to the stars.  Neither one of us could quite spot that, but it is an impressive formation.  Our lunch stop was in the largest town on the island, Portree.  There were tourists everywhere and the restaurants were all full.  We ended up with soup and bread at a local bakery, sharing an outside picnic table with some friendly Australians on holiday.  Honesty, there is no way our photos can capture the vast landscapes of Skye.  </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
