<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>problems &#8211; Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/problems/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 01:52:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2021 &#8211; Lake Medina Thousand Trails &#8211; Lakehills, TX</title>
		<link>/2021/08/23/2021-lake-medina-thousand-trails-lakehills-tx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thousand Trails]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pastorscott.com/travel/?p=4794</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We had an interesting stay at Medina Lake Thousand Trails in Lakehills, TX. This campground has a variety of campsite amenities ranging from 30 amp with no sewer up to full hookup 50 amp sites. The various campsite configurations are scattered around the large campground with no seeming rhyme or reason. Also, many sites are [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><figure id="attachment_4796" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4796" style="width: 960px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/IMG_20210803_102056-1024x576.jpg" alt="" width="960" height="540" class="size-large wp-image-4796" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/IMG_20210803_102056-1024x576.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/IMG_20210803_102056-300x169.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/IMG_20210803_102056-768x432.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/IMG_20210803_102056-1536x865.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/IMG_20210803_102056.jpg 1734w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-4796" class="wp-caption-text">2021 &#8211; Medina Lake Thousand Trails &#8211; Lakehills, TX</figcaption></figure><br />
We had an interesting stay at Medina Lake Thousand Trails in Lakehills, TX.  This campground has a variety of campsite amenities ranging from 30 amp with no sewer up to full hookup 50 amp sites.  The various campsite configurations are scattered around the large campground with no seeming rhyme or reason.  Also, many sites are somewhat unlevel.  We needed to take the motorhome into the shop (more on that later) so we took advantage of the move to relocate to a more level site.</p>
<p><a href="/2014/11/01/campground-review-medina-lake-thousand-trails-lakehills-tx/">A previous review is here.</a></p>
<p>Medina Lake Thousand Trails is known for two things: deer everywhere and a lake that is more often than not lacking in water.  We found both to be true on this trip.  The deer are practically tame and watch you expectantly, hoping to be fed.  People do feed the deer, but the campground and the local game warden frown on doing so because it changes the behavior and the diet of the deer.  The lake is more of a small, shallow river as it borders the campground.  Closer to the dam there is more water, but the lake is still quite low.  Really, it takes a lot of rain over a relatively small area to feed Medina Lake.  The area is still beautiful hill country, one of our favorite parts of Texas.</p>
<p>As I said, we took the RV in for service and the report was not a good one.  As a result our home had to go into the shop to repair a crack in the black water tank (ugh!).  When we upgraded our Thousand Trails membership we were given a few years of one week cabin stays.  We moved into a one bedroom cabin, claiming the week and then extending it as work was done on the RV.  The cabin wasn&#8217;t as comfortable as our motorhome, but we did fine in it.  </p>
<p>The campground is undergoing electric upgrades.  In fact, there are many new power pedestals already in place.  Large sections of the campground have the new service.  However, during our stay no new 50 amp service was available.  Apparently, they await a final county inspection (or something like that).  Until then, all the new 50 amp breakers have locks on them.  I don&#8217;t think any sewer upgrades are planned so even after the upgraded sites become available you still need to note which sites have sewer and which do not.  </p>
<p>Aside from the deer, the lake (when wet), and the pretty hill country the campground has a nice pool, small playground, Activity Center (nothing happening there because of Covid), mini-golf, and laundry.  Bandera is nearby with lots of Cowboy themed stores, restaurants, and events.  San Antonio is a bit farther, but is a great tourist city.</p>
<p>This review actually covers two stays, a month apart, at Medina Lake.  During our second stay we spent some time in San Antonio, revisiting some spots we enjoyed when we lived there several years ago.  The campground isn&#8217;t especially close to San Antonio, but downtown is just over an hour away.</p>
<p>We enjoyed the OST Restaurant in Bandera and worshiping at the nearby Western Heritage Cowboy Church.  Walmart just off of Culebra Road in San Antonio is a distance away.  I had no big problem getting a satellite signal but that would be site dependent.  My Verizon was pretty good at 2-3 bars.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQVwZqJ7WCjMzXMEMmHWmvD1eq3PJmMQbOvebCDwK2OkJMOGiFW-pzv80Tno32zy8jf5nLKn_cMj45i/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="480" height="299" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
