<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Connecticut - Here and There</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/connecticut/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Scott and Jackie&#039;s Travels – Thousand Trails Reviews, Campground Reviews, Fulltime RVing, European Travel</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 23:51:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2018 &#8211; Bear Creek Campground &#8211; Bristol, CT</title>
		<link>/2018/08/20/2018-bear-creek-campground-bristol-ct/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[grscott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 23:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[camping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Connecticut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shortstop]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.pastorscott.com/travel/?p=3226</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lake Compounce in Bristol, Connecticut is the oldest continually operating amusement park in the United States. The park recently added a Bear Creek Campground that features cabins, teepees, a tenting area, and, of course, a large RV area. The campsites are laid out with water-electric hookups located in a shared grassy area on the driver&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/2018/08/20/2018-bear-creek-campground-bristol-ct/">2018 – Bear Creek Campground – Bristol, CT</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-lmnurmbbJiI/W3tOLpBtExI/AAAAAAAA1Ts/4wD_15wnv9YzBLxUckI_385dzEIoyljxwCKgBGAs/s1600/IMG_20180820_170452.jpg" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-large" /><br />
Lake Compounce in Bristol, Connecticut is the oldest continually operating amusement park in the United States.  The park recently added a Bear Creek Campground that features cabins, teepees, a tenting area, and, of course, a large RV area.  The campsites are laid out with water-electric hookups located in a shared grassy area on the driver&#8217;s side of the sites.  If the place is full, there will be a shared front yard between campers as well.  Most people, I think, come to spend a few days at the amusement park.  There&#8217;s even a shuttle operating from the campground to the main gate of the park.  </p>
<p>Our shortstop stay was just for one night as we traveled from southern Maine into Pennsylvania.  The campground is about 10 minutes from I84 and the campsites are all pull-through, making it a handy place for an overnight stay.  When I asked about discounts the lady I talked to on the phone offered me a nightly rate based on a three night stay rather than just one night.  </p>
<p>Here are a few things you might want to know.  The sites are all water/electric (30/50 amp), no sewer.  Individual shower rooms are available.  There is campground WiFi &#8211; ours got slower as the evening progressed.  There&#8217;s a nearby power plant that can be heard non-stop in the near distance.  </p>
<p>I had a strong 4G signal and, since the campsites are pretty much out in the open, satellite TV is no problem.    The campground has a play area, but the main recreation is the amusement park.  I think Bear Creek is a good choice for a stop in the Bristol, CT area.</p>
<p><center><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQffPlMl_tRY50l15tc9IY0kkCOEihp5cblkmTuFdgi4aRV4w2qM2hsaB39zDVdZFUIl4zh2o0ZrKjH/embed?start=true&#038;loop=true&#038;delayms=3000" frameborder="0" width="960" height="569" allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe><br />
<a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/UBKEKr71YJNYpGANA">See individual photos with captions here.</a></center></p><p>The post <a href="/2018/08/20/2018-bear-creek-campground-bristol-ct/">2018 – Bear Creek Campground – Bristol, CT</a> first appeared on <a href="">Here and There</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
